export default Question_Data =  [
{ 
    question: 'Which among the following is not a correct pair?',
    options: ['Ellora Caves', 'Mahabalipuram','hajuraho ','Elephanta Caves'],
    current_ans : 'Elephanta Caves',
},
{ 
    question: 'Upnishads are books on :',
    options: ['Politics', 'Philosophy','Medicine','Social life'],
    current_ans : 'Philosophy',
},
{ 
    question: 'Who was the first Indian ruler who had territory outside India?',
    options: ['Ashoka', 'Chandragupta Maurya','Kanishka','Huvishka'],
    current_ans : 'Kanishka',
},
{ 
    question: 'Who was the last Hindu emperor of northern India?',
    options: ['Harsha', 'Pulakesin II','Rajyavardhana ','Skandagupta'],
    current_ans : 'Harsha',
},
{ 
    question: 'Which among the following is not a correct pair?',
    options: ['Ellora Caves', 'Mahabalipuram','hajuraho ','Elephanta Caves'],
    current_ans : 'Elephanta Caves',
},
{ 
    question: 'Microprocessor was introduced in which generation of computer?',
    options: ['First Generation', 'Second Generation','Third Generation ','Fourth Generation'],
    current_ans : 'Fourth Generation',
},
{ 
    question: 'The first generation computers were used between ____',
    options: ['1940 - 1955', '1940 - 1956','1941 - 1956','1941 - 1955'],
    current_ans : '1940 - 1956',
},
{ 
    question: 'The CPU is called the ___ of the computer.',
    options: ['Mind', 'Brain','Heart','Hand'],
    current_ans : 'Brain',
},
{ 
    question: 'What is the full form of "kbps"?.',
    options: ['Kilobytes Per Second', 'Kilobits Per Second','Kilobeats Per Second','Kilobeats Per Second'],
    current_ans : 'Kilobytes Per Second',
},
{ 
    question: 'Transferring your HTML code from one machine to server is known as ___',
    options: ['Indexing', 'Hosting','Serving','Sorting'],
    current_ans : 'Hosting',
},



]